Crime runs in the family.
Blood Ties is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by Guillaume Canet.
Two brothers, on either side of the law, face off over
organized crime in Brooklyn during the 1970s.
Chris Pierzynski, played by Clive Owen.
Frank, played by Billy Crudup.
Monica, played by Marion Cotillard.
Natalie, played by Mila Kunis.
Vanessa, played by Zoe Saldaña.
Anthony Scarfo, played by Matthias Schoenaerts.
Blood Ties is a 2013 crime thriller film directed by Guillaume Canet and starring Clive
Owen, Billy Crudup, Marion Cotillard, Mila Kunis and Matthias Schoenaerts.
It is a remake of the 2008 French thriller film Les liens du sang by Jacques Maillot, an
adaptation of the French novel Deux frères: flic & truand by Bruno and Michel Papet.
The screenplay was written by Canet and James Gray.
The film was selected to be screened out of
competition at the 2013 Cannes Film Festival.
The film is a co-production between France and the United States.
It was released in France by Mars Distribution on October 30, 2013, and by
Roadside Attractions in the United States on March 21, 2014.
The tone is emotional and intense.